Narrator: 1
Speaker: …and having fewer people in the office may simply not be an option,
not to mention that many employees may not want a drop in salary
in exchange for a shorter working week.
Narrator: 2
Speaker: In particular,
people who were religious about taking short breaks were far more productive
than those who worked longer hours.
Narrator: 3
Speaker: They discovered that the ideal work-to-break ratio was 52 minutes of work,
followed by 18 minutes of rest.
Narrator: 4
Speaker: Apart from getting you into the right rhythm,
planning your day around hour-long intervals simplifies daunting tasks
by breaking them into manageable chunks.
Narrator: 5
Speaker: If you want to follow the research recommendations to the letter,
you can plan your day around 52-minute intervals if you like, but an hour works just as well.